

ANDRÉS SANHUEZA

Frontend Developer

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Gjøvik, Norway

PHONE

46 54 89 62

EMAIL

trazo263@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/aisanhueza

SKILLS

Javascript • HTML • CSS3 SASS • ReactJst • Redux • AngularJs • React Native • Typescript

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

Advanced

SPANISH

Native speaker

PROFILE

I'm a FrontEnd Developer with a Designer background. I majored in design, taught myself how to code in Javascript, and I've being working as a FrontEnd dev for the past 5 years. I like to build beautiful and functional digital products.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cheetrack

FrontEnd Developer (Feb 2021 - Present) Santiago, Chile

- Development and web design for the Cheetrack web app, a communication solution that integrates chat platforms like WhatsApp with sales and checkout data from Shopify.
- ReactJs, Redux, Material UI, CSS in JS, Webhooks, API Rest.

Conectter

FrontEnd Developer (Oct 2017 - Feb 2021) Santiago, Chile

- Development and web design for the Conectter web app, a project and task management solution.
- AngularJS, Pug/Jade, SASS, API Rest.

EDUCATION

Design (2011 - 2015)

Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile (Santiago, Chile)

Sociology (2008 - 2010)

Universidad Alberto Hurtado (Santiago, Chile)